Professional and personal papers of Edwin Wolf 2nd LCP.EW2
Library Company of Philadelphia
- III. Scholarship, Bulk, 1945-1988; 1833-1996
  - IIIb. Research, Bulk, 1945-1988; 1833-1996
    - Philadelphia Charter: Galley proofs of “The 1706 Charter of Philadelphia,” Proceedings of the American Philosophical Society, XC 388-405 [1952]; and typescript copy of the introduction, circa 1952 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Philadelphia Charter: Letters between Edwin and Gertrude D. Hess, W. E. Lingelbach, Logan Fox, Horace Wolf, T. R. Adams, R. N. Williams II, W. Jackson, W. W. Comfort, G. W. Pepper, L. M. Stevens, J. C. Wylie, C. K. Shipton, L. E. Bliss, K. M. Ruckman, Keyes D. Metcalf, John F. Lewis, F. R. Mann, B. W. Korn, and Mrs. Ruth M. Reese (20 items), 1952 October 15-1953 January 12 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Philadelphia Charter: Typescript copy and research notes for article, circa 1952 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Philadelphia Charter: Unedited version of article, circa 1952 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Philadelphia Charter: Thank you notes from various libraries and publishers for receipt of article (15 items), circa 1952 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Poe and Horace Wemyss Smith: Letters between Edwin and W. VanLemmen and R. Hirsch; draft copy of “Horace Wemyss Smith's Recollections of Poe”, 1950 December 29-1951 December 3 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Poe and Horace Wemyss Smith: Typescript drafts and copy of “Horace Wemyss Smith's Recollections of Poe,” published in The Library Chronicle, XVII 90-103 [1951]; and research notes, circa 1951 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Pollock papers: 14 letters between Edwin and George P. Hammond, M. Withington. J. T. Babb, R. W. G. Vail, S. T. Riley, Mabel R. Gillis, Mr. Sherman, E. Euphrat, and Tulane University Library, 1948 April 5-1949 April 19 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Pollock papers: 25 letters between Edwin and Jacob R. Marchs, Mearns, Meyer Solis-Cohen, C. K. Shipton, Carnegie Library, and Rabbi I. Meyer, 1949 April 26-1950 May 25 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Pollock papers: Letters between Edwin and Marcus W. Price, T. Streetcar, Ellen Rackstraw, Miss W. Allen, Lamar C. Wallace, E. Euphrant, and Mildrid Stephenson; hand-drawn Pollock family tree; photocopy of "Proposals, Addressed to Those Who Possess a Public Spirit," owned by Pollock, 1949 July 27-1950 July 6, undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Polock papers; writings: Draft 1, The Polocks: Philadelphia adventurers and pioneers, 1833-1854. Typesecript, with mss. corrections and additions in pencil and ink. Begins: "The Polock Brothers, born in Philadelphia...", undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Polock papers; writings: Draft 2, The Polocks: Philadelphia adventurers and pioneers, 1833-1854. Typescript, on onionskin. Begins: "The Polock brothers, born in Philadelphia...", undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Polock papers; writings: Draft 3, The Polocks: Philadelphia adventurers and pioneers, 1833-1854. Typescript, on typing paper. Begins: "The Polock brothers, born in Philadelphia...", undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Polock papers; writings: Draft A, The Polocks: American adventurers and pioneers, 1833-1854. Typescript, with mss. corrections and additions in pencil and ink. Begins: "To those interested in the printed records of American Jewish history..." Introduction., undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Polock papers; writings: "Notes to letter 2." Typescript, with ink annotations, Draft A [?], undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Polock papers; writings: Draft B, The Polocks: American adventurers and pioneers, 1833-1854. Typescript, with mss. corrections and additions in pencil and ink. Begins: "To those interested in the printed records of American Jewish history..." Introduction, Parts I, II, notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Polock papers; writings: Draft B. Documents 1-14, with notes, corrected in pencil and ink, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Polock papers; writings: Draft B. Documents 15-19, with notes, corrected in pencil and ink, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Polock papers; writings: Draft B. Notes to Document 20, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Polock papers; writings: Draft B. Part III-A California Pioneer, with notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Polock papers; writings: Draft B. Documents 20-28 with notes, corrected in pencil and ink [2 copies of document 20], undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Polock papers; writings: Draft B. Document 27; 2 copies, with manuscript corrections, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Polock papers; writings: Draft B. Documents 29-40, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Polock papers; writings: Draft B. Documents 41-71, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Polock papers; writings: Draft B. Typed notes for documents 50-57, annotated in pencil, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Polock papers; writings: Draft C. Typescript of The Polocks: American adventurers and pioneers, 1833-1845. Introduction, notes, and documents 1-14. Manuscript notes in pencil and ink, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Polock papers; writings: Draft C. Part III, A California Pioneer, notes, documents 15-28 with notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Polock papers; writings: Draft C. Part IV--Halcyon Years in Galveston. Lined paper, typed. Annotated in ink, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Polock papers; writings: Draft C. Typescript of Part 4 (fragment). Begins: "which time he came back to Galveston. John Dyer's wife...", undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Polock papers; writings: Draft C. Document 26, 2 copies, mss corrections, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Polock papers; writings: Draft C. Typescript notes to document 29, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Polock papers; writings: Draft C. Documents 29-41. Annotated in pencil and ink, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Polock papers; writings: Draft C. Notes for documents 29-36, typed with pencil annotations, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Polock papers; writings: Draft C. Documents 42-48 [another copy], undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Polock papers; writings: Draft C. Documents 50-71, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Polock papers; manuscript notes: Manuscript notes, in pencil. "Abraham bar shimon ha-levi [Abraham Simon Wolf] to Marim bat Haim.", undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Polock papers; manuscript notes: Manuscript notes, in pencil. "Arrived at N.O., Tuesday Dec 11 Wheeler, p. 20", undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Polock papers; manuscript notes: Manuscript notes in pencil. Bibliographic, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Polock papers; manuscript notes: Manuscript notes in pencil and ink. Polock and Levy family trees, with addenda, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Polock papers; manuscript notes: Manuscript in ink. Binswanger family tree, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Polock papers; manuscript notes: Manuscript notes in pencil and ink. "Capt. Elliot...", undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Polock papers; manuscript notes: Manuscript notes in pencil and ink, "John M. Dyer...", undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Polock papers; manuscript notes: Manuscript notes in pencil. "Mayer Arnold-elected...", undated (Box 1, Folder 31b)
    - Polock papers; manuscript notes: Manuscript notes in ink. Newspapers, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Polock papers; manuscript notes: Manuscript notes in pencil and ink. Philadephia Directory listings, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Polock papers; manuscript notes: Manuscript notes on notebook paper: "Thirtieth Congress. Sess. II Ch. 107. 1849". "An act to carry into effect certain stipulations of the Treaty between U.S. of Amer., the Rep. of Mexico, of the second day of February, one thousand, eight hundred, forty-eight.", undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Polock papers; manuscript notes: Typed transcript of ms. letter with notes, M. S. Polock to Hyman Polock [Oct 4, 1843], annotated in pencil. Begins "Amsterdam, Eve of Yom Kippur, 5604.", undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Polock papers; typescript notes: Typescript, "California State Library/Sacramento 9/Lewis Pollock.", undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Polock papers; typescript notes: Typed notes, with chronology (?) of Lewis Polock, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Polock papers; typescript notes: Typescript, "[Copied from photostat from the Alta California, June 25, 1851, p. 2, c. 2-3]", undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Polock papers; typescript notes: Typescript, "[Copied from photostat from the Alta California, June 25, 1851, p. 2, c. 2-3]" [another copy], undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Polock papers; typescript notes: Typed notes. "Deed Book E. Center Co. p. 286", undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Polock papers; typescript notes: Typed notes, annotated in pencil. "Frank M. Pixley was born...", undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Polock papers; typescript notes: Typescript fragment: "From the 1820s on there existed a permanent settlement at Galveston...", undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Polock papers; typescript notes: Typescript notes: "History of the San Francisco Committee of Vigilance of 1851", undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Polock papers; typescript notes: Typed biography of Isadore Dyer (sent by Rosenberg Library, Galveston TX), undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Polock papers; typescript notes: Typed index cards. "Isthmus Crossing--cost of", undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Polock papers; typescript notes: Typescript notes: "John White Geary Soldier Statesman 1819-1973", undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Polock papers; typescript notes: Typed notes, on California State Library letterhead, "Lewis Pollock", undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Polock papers; typescript notes: Typed notes: List of prisoners [?], attachments D, E, F, undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Polock papers; typescript notes: Typed notes, with corrections in ink, 8 May 1950: "MEMORANDUM re: Galveston Newspapers, 1838-1854...", 1950 May 8, undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Polock papers; typescript notes: Typed notes, "PAJHS, No. 2, Cohen Settlement of the Jews in Texas, p. 145...", undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Polock papers; typescript notes: Typed notes with pencil annotations. Polock family and descendents (not correspondent brothers), undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Polock papers; typescript notes: Notes: Typescript. Manuscript [Robinson], undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Polock papers; typescript notes: Typescript. "Royall Tyler Wheeler", undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Polock papers; typescript notes: Typescript. "Samuel May Williams", undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Polock papers; typescript notes: Typescript page: "Today the Jewish community of the United States...", undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Polock papers; typescript notes: Typed notes, and pencil annotations. "Up to 1835...", undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Polock papers; typescript notes: Typed draft. "When Oregon became a part of the United States in 1846...", undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Polock papers; photostats/clippings: Photostats Alta California, June 25, 1851, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Polock papers; photostats/clippings: Newspaper clipping. Galveston Daily News, May 28, 1950. "Scion of Pioneers Recalls Early Days", 1950 May 28 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Polock papers; photostats/clippings: Photostat. "Lewis Pollock" on California State Library/Sacramento 9 letterhead; source: American Jewish Archives [stamp on back], undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Polock papers; photostats/clippings: Photostats. National Archives, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Polock papers; photostats/clippings: Photostat. Newspaper, undated (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Polock papers; photostats/clippings: Photostats. Records of Boundary and Claims Commission. Photostat of signed original of document 23, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Ms. letter, signed, J. Burnford Samual to "Messrs. Rosenbach," with envelope, "The story of Rachel Levy", undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Jacob R. Marcus to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1948 March 20 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, Rosenbach Company to Irvin L. Stone, 1913 April 19 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Jacob R. Marcus per F. Friedman to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1948 May 20 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, Edwin Wolf 2nd to Jacob R. Marcus, 1948 May 28 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, Nancy Kimball Leib to Carl C. Cutler, 1948 May 28 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Carl C. Cutler to Nancy Kimball Leib, 1948 May 29 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, Nancy Kimball Leib to Paul C. Nicholson, 1948 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, Nancy Kimball Leib to Nantucket Whaling Museum, 1948 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, Edwin Wolf 2nd to Union Library Catalogue, 1948 June 2 (Box 2, Folder 9a)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Jacob R. Marcus to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1948 June 3 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Miriam L. Towler to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1948 June 3 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Polock papers, research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Paul C. Nicholson to Nancy Kimball Leib, 1948 June 4 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, J. Solis Cohen to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1949 March 22 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Polock papers, research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Harry Polish to J. Solis Cohen, Jr., 1949 March 23 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Laurence G. Gill to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1949 March 30 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Mabel R. Gillis to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1949 March 31 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Stuart C. Sherman to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1949 April 2 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Dorothy C. Barck to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1949 April 9 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Elizabeth Euphrat (and George P. Hammond) to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1949 April 9 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Elizabeth Euphrat to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1949 April 23 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Joe W. Kraus to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1949 April 23 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Jacob R. Marcus to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1949 May 2 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, David C. Mearns to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1949 May 31 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, with photostat enclosure, Bertha Lauter [secretary to Jacob Marcus] to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1949 July 28 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Jacob R. Marcus to Edwin Wolf 2nd, with carbon of typed letter, JRM to Isidore Meyers, 1949 August 2 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, with carbon enclosures, Jacob R. Marcus to Edwin Wolf, 2nd, 1949 August 2 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Jacob R. Marcus to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1949 August 9 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed notes, JRM [Jacob R. Marcus] to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1949 August 9 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Isidore S. Meyer to Jacob R. Marcus, 1949 August 11 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Jacob R. Marcus to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1949 August 16 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Florence [Weinstein?] to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1949 August 18 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Jacob R. Marcus to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1949 August 25 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Autograph letter, signed, Myer (Solis-Cohen] to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1949 September 4 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Clifford K. Shapiro to Edwin Wolf 2nd, with enclosure, 1949 September 9 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Isidore Meyer to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1949 September 16 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Clifford K. Shipton to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1949 September 16 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Jacob Marcus to Edwin Wolf 2nd. With copies of Seat Records from Mikve Israel, 1949 September 23 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Rose Demorest to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1949 October 10 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Jacob R. Marcus to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1950 January 11 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Isidore Meyer to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1950 May 3 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Thomas W. Streeter to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1950 May 9 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Isidore Meyer to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1950 May 28 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Jacob R. Marcus to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1950 May 29 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed "Extract from letter received from Israel T. Naamani to Jacob Marcus, June 13, 1950", undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, C. Lamar Willis to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1950 June 14 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Mildred Stevenson to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1950 June 28 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Mildred Stevenson to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1950 June 30 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Malcolm H. Stern to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1950 October 11 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, "copy," [Edwin Wolf 2nd?] to Herbert I. Bloom, 1950 December 1 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Jacob R. Marcus to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1950 December 14 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Jacob R. Marcus to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1950 December 21 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Isidore Meyer to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1951 January 9 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, James A. Shackford [?] to Edwin Wolf 2nd. With mss. postscript, 1951 November 30 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, Charles S. Bernheimer to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1952 March 15 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Polock papers; research correspondence and notes: Typed letter, signed, John F. Graf to Edwin Wolf 2nd, 1989 October 28 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Hyman Polock, Columbia. Original of Document 1, 1833 August 23 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Sarah Polock, Lewistown. Original of Document 2., 1834 January 25 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Hyman and Rebecca Polock, New Orleans. Original of Document 3, 1834 December 21 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Sarah Polock, New Orleans. Original of Document 4, 1835 May 10 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Sarah Polock, New Orleans. Original of Document 5, 1835 May 25 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Hyman Polock, New Orleans. Original of Document 6, 1835 July 5 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Sarah Polock, Pittsburgh. Original of Document 7, 1835 November 3 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Hyman Polock, New Orleans. Original of Document 8, 1835 November 19 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Hyman Polock, Mobile. Original of Document 9, 1835 December 5 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Sarah Polock, Claiborne. Original of Document 10, 1836 April 9 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Sarah Polock, Claiborne. Original of Document 11, 1836 July 16 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Sarah Polock, Claiborne. Original of Document 12, 1836 September 6 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Sarah Polock, Claiborne. Original of Document 13, 1839 September 15 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Sarah Polock, Claiborne. Original of Document 14, 1840 December 25 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Lewis to Hyman Polock, Tepic. Original of Document 18, 1842 June 6 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Lewis to Hyman Polock [1841?]. Original of Document 19, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript document, signed, Lewis Polock, to Barnett Polock [Power of attorney], Republic of Mexico. Original of Document 21, 1848 April 21 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, J. A. Phillips to I. Binswanger, South Sixth Street (Phila.). Original of Document 22, 1850 May 7 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Document by Lewis Polock, San Francisco. Unsigned manuscript [holograph] original of Document 23. "Memorial of Lewis Polock" [Probably a copy enclosed with Polock family copy of Lewis's power of attorney, also unsigned]., 1850 July 10, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Power of Attorney by Lewis Polock [unsigned copy]. Original of Document 24, 1850 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Solomon to Hyman and Sarah Polock, Galveston. Original of Document 29, 1842 January 25 (Box 3, Folder 19)